Do you ever feel like nothing you do matters?
你是否感到过自己所做的都毫无意义
You leave footprints on the beach,
就像在海滩上留下的脚印
and tomorrow they're gone.
第二天便消失不见
Like it's just today over again.
就像不断重复的一天又一天
They say your teen years
人们说十几岁时
are for making friends and having fun...
就是要交朋友、尽情玩耍
which made me feel even worse.
对我来说这样更糟
Hey, Amy. It's Jake.
嗨，艾米，我是杰克
I'm in your math class.
咱俩数学课一起上
Hey, don't forget your adult diapers.
嘿，别忘了给自己买成人纸尿裤
Yeah, right.
呵呵
Jake. Phone for you.
杰克，有电话找你
But that day, everything changed.
但那一天开始，一切都变了
Thanks for the ride, Shelley.
谢谢你送我，雪莉
So, how come you have to go deal with your grandpa?
怎么让你去照顾你爷爷呢？
My dad couldn't get out of work.
我爸他工作忙，走不开
I didn't think he worked.
他还有工作？
I'm just gonna call Grandpa.
我还是给爷爷打个电话吧
Hello, this is Abe.
我是亚伯
Hey, it's Jake.
我是杰克
No! Don't come here. Listen to me.
别过来！听我说
It's not safe.
这里不安全
Stay away.
千万别来
Grandpa, did you take your pills today?
爷爷，你今天吃药了吗？
The key to my gun cabinet, it was in the drawer.
放枪的橱柜的钥匙，本来在抽屉里
And now it's gone.
现在不见了！
Yeah, Dad took it, all right?
我爸拿走了，你不记得了？
For safekeeping. It's okay.
安全起见，好吧
Your father wants I should fight them without a gun?
你爸拿走了？没有枪我怎么对付他们？
God bless him.
上帝保佑他
What's his deal, Alzheimer's?
他是怎么了？老年痴呆？
Dementia.
智力衰弱
That guy gave me the heebie-jeebies.
那家伙吓我一跳
Holler if you need me.
有什么事就喊我
Grandpa?
爷爷？
Shelley!
雪莉！
What's goin' on?
怎么回事？
Someone broke in.
有人闯进来了
I've got a.38 in my car. You wait there.
我车里有枪，在这儿等我
Grandpa!
爷爷！
911. What's your emergency?
911，您遇到了什么紧急情况？
911? Yeah, I need the paramedics.
我需要医务人员
It's at 2040 Palm Circle. My grandpa...
地址是棕榈环路2040号，我爷爷…
Sir, what's your emergency?
您遇到了什么紧急情况？
Grandpa.
爷爷
You have to get away from here.
你得赶快走
Sir, can you hear me?
能听见我说话吗，先生？
Please. Listen.
听我说
Go to the island.
去岛上
Sir, paramedics are on their way.
先生，医务人员正在赶来
Find Emerson.
找到艾默生
The postcard.
那张明信片
Go to the loop.
找到圈
September 3rd, 1943.
1943年9月3号
It's okay.
没事的
Just don't move. There's an ambulance coming.
不要动，救护车马上来了
I know you think I'm crazy.
你肯定觉得我疯了
But the bird will explain everything.
但鸟会跟你解释的
Will you do this, Tygrysku? Promise me?
答应我，小老虎，你一定去
I promise, yes.
我一定去
I thought I could protect you.
我以为自己能保护你
I should have told you years ago.
我早就应该告诉你
Grandpa. Tell me what?
爷爷！告诉我什么？
Grandpa!
爷爷！
Shelley, behind you!
雪莉，小心后面
There was no one there.
那里没有人
May I say, Jake...
听我说，杰克…
that considering this was only a month ago...
鉴于才过去一个月
I think you're doing exceptionally well.
我认为你的表现已经很好了
Apart from being crazy?
你是说不疯了？
Having nightmares and anxiety doesn't make you crazy.
做恶梦和焦虑并不代表你疯了
What about seeing things which aren't there?
那看到并不存在的东西呢？
Actually, in traumatic situations,
在某些特殊情况下
it's not at all uncommon.
这种现象也很常见
Your subconscious mind drew an image from a movie or...
你头脑中的潜意识会提取电影中的画面，或是…
It was a story.
是因为一个故事
My grandpa told me stories when I was a kid...
我小时候，爷爷会给我讲故事
about monsters that he fought in the war.
讲他在战争中遇到的那些怪物
So there you go.
你看
He was brutally attacked...
他当时伤的很重
and in your head, the man who did it was inhuman, a monster.
所以你认为伤他的是非人类，是怪物
It wasn't a man, though.
不过也不是人
The cops said that dogs
警察说纱门上
scratched up the screen door...
有狗抓过的痕迹
and he chased them off into the woods.
他追到树林里
And the coroner said he had a heart attack.
验尸官说他当时心脏病发作
And the cops said...
警察说
that dogs go for the soft parts.
狗会吃掉尸体软组织
They DNA tested the fork...
他们检查了叉子上提取到的DNA
and it had animal DNA.
里面有动物的DNA
So, that's case closed.
就这么结案了
He sounds like an extraordinary gentleman.
听你说的，你爷爷应该是个了不起的人
Were you very close?
你俩很亲近吗？
Puerto Rico.
波多黎各
Here.
这里
There's a lake where the water glows in the dark.
那里有个湖，湖水晚上会发光
And a secret tunnel.
还有一个秘密通道
That's where I hid from the monsters.
我藏在里面躲过了怪物
He used to babysit me a lot.
我小时候他经常照顾我
When I was with him, I felt special.
跟他在一起的时候，我有种特别的感觉
My duck was dry again.
我的鸭子又干了
Abe. It's, like, 11:00. What is he doing up?
亚伯，都11点了，他怎么还没睡
I'm gonna be an explorer.
我要当一个探险家
Grandpa's helping me plan my first voyage.
爷爷在帮我计划第一次航行
Everything's already been discovered, buddy.
世上的角角落落都已经被探过了
They terrorize each other...
他们恐吓彼此
before wreaking havoc on the rest of the island.
然后大肆破坏，毁掉了岛上的其他地方
Pay no attention to your father.
别理你爸爸
He knows bubkes.
他什么都不知道
Come, Tygrysku. Off to bed.
走吧，小老虎，该睡了
Can you tell me a story?
给我讲个故事吧
The usual?
经常讲的那个？
Okay. Once upon a time...
很久很久以前
there was a little boy...
有一个小男孩
With the pictures.
要带图片
Pictures.
图片啊
Once upon a time...
很久很久以前
there was a little boy called Abe.
有个小男孩名叫亚伯
That was you.
就是你嘛
That was me.
是我
And he lived in a lovely children's home
他住在一个很美丽的福利院
on a little island near Wales...
就在威尔士附近一座小岛上
where the sun shone every day.
那里每天都阳光灿烂
The headmistress, Miss Peregrine...
那里的女校长叫佩瑞格林小姐
was very clever.
她非常非常聪明
And she smoked a pipe.
她还抽烟斗
She could turn into a bird.
她还能变成鸟
It was a home for special children...
那里是特殊儿童之家
like Bronwyn and Victor.
比如布朗温，还有维克多
They were both as strong as 10 men.
他俩都非常强壮，比得过十个壮汉
And Hugh...
还有休
Hugh had bees living inside him.
休身体住着蜜蜂
Where's Emma?
艾玛呢？
She could float.
她会飘起来
She was lighter than air.
她比空气还轻
She had to wear special shoes made of lead
必须得穿上铅做的鞋子
to keep her from floating away.
否则会飘走
Where is she now?
她现在在哪里？
She's still on the island, I believe.
应该还在岛上吧
My mama and papa sent me there...
我的爸爸妈妈把我送到那里
to live with the special children.
和特殊的小孩子们一起生活
And now, Tygrysku, time for sleep.
小老虎该睡觉了
He used to call me Tygrysku.
他总是叫我小老虎
It's Polish for "little tiger."
就是波兰语的小老虎的意思
He couldn't have picked a less appropriate nickname.
一点都不像我
I was always a chicken.
我那时候胆子很小
Why did your mom and dad send you away?
你的爸爸妈妈为什么把你送走
Well, where we lived in Poland, it wasn't safe.
我们那时住在波兰，那里不安全
There were monsters.
那里有怪物
What kind of monsters?
哪种怪物？
Huge ones, with long arms...
超级大的怪物，有很长的手臂
and no eyes...
没有眼睛
and tentacles like this.
触手就像这样
The dumb thing was...
可笑的是
for years, I actually believed his stories.
好多年，我都相信他的故事
And this is Millard. He's invisible.
这个是米勒德，他是隐形人
My teacher says they were trick photos.
老师说那些照片是专门唬人的
And did you believe her?
你相信她说的吗？
Dad says you probably found them
爸爸说你大概是在某家
at a junk store someplace...
旧货商店找到的
when you went traveling.
就在你旅行的时候
I would never lie to you, Tygrysku.
我永远不会骗你，小老虎
But you did, about the home, the monsters.
但是你就是骗我了，福利院，还有怪物
Dad told me.
爸爸说
Your father knows very well
你爸爸知道
I went to live in the children's home.
我小时候住在儿童之家
He said there really were monsters in Poland...
他说那时候波兰的确有怪物
just not the kind with tentacles.
但不是长触角的那种怪物
He said you got sent to Wales 'cause there were bad people.
他说你被送去威尔士是因为波兰有坏人
People who wanted to kill anyone who was different.
那些人会杀掉所有跟他们不一样的人
I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
我不想继续谈这个了
He said the children were special...
他说那里的孩子是很特殊
but not the way you said.
但不是你说的那种特殊
You find something good?
发现什么好东西了？
Oh, look at that. That's awesome.
哦，快瞧瞧，真棒
You should take that.
带走吧
Come on, buddy, let's roll.
走吧，小伙子
How are you so okay?
你怎么跟没事儿人一样？
Jakey, you were a lot closer to him than I ever was.
杰克，你跟爷爷的关系比我跟他亲近多了
He was a wonderful grandpa...
他是个好爷爷
but not such a great dad.
但不算是个好爸爸
Never seemed to pick a job...
他所有的工作
that didn't involve late nights
都早出晚归
or long trips away, though.
还经常出差很久
Me and Aunt Susie always kind of thought
我和你苏希姑姑
he was, maybe, cheating on our mom.
都以为他出轨了
I'm sorry, buddy. I know how much you worshiped him...
对不起，我知道你很崇拜爷爷
but there it is.
但事实就是这样
Surprise!
惊喜吧！！
Happy birthday, Cousin Jake!
生日快乐，杰克表哥
J-dog, it's great you're coming
杰克，真高兴
to spend a summer with us.
你暑假和我们一起过
Wait till you see the new boat.
等会儿带你去看新船
Can't wait.
很期待呢
It's Aunt Susie.
是苏希姑姑
Thought you might wanna open this one.
我猜这个礼物你会喜欢
It's from your grandpa.
是爷爷送你的
Found it while I was packing up.
我看到的时候已经包好了
I figured he meant to give it to you someday.
我猜他是想给你的
Thanks.
谢谢姑姑
To Jake, and the worlds he has yet to discover.
致杰克，以及他即将发现的世界
My dearest Abe...
最最亲爱的亚伯
I hope this card finds you well.
希望你能收到这张卡片
The children and I yearn to hear your news.
孩子们和我都非常想你
I do hope you will visit us again soon.
希望你很快能再来看望我们
We should so love to see you.
我们都非常期待见到你
With admiration...
此致
Alma Peregrine.
阿尔玛·佩瑞格林
H mm. Only two years ago.
呃…两年前寄来的
I suppose it's possible she could still be alive.
很可能她还活着
Right.
对
I could meet her.
我可以见见她
Maybe even find out what it was
也许能发现
Grandpa wanted me to know.
爷爷想让我知道的事情
But what if she's dead?
但是如果她死了呢？
Dr. Golan...
格兰医生
we are very concerned
我们很关心
with Jake's state of mind right now.
杰克现在的心理状况
There's no way I'm putting my life on hold
我没法放下工作
to take you to Wales.
带你去威尔士啊
Dad could take me.
爸爸可以带我去
And he can look at birds...
他可以去看鸟…
and work on his book.
顺便完成他的书
It means you get a break.
你也能休息一段时间
As Dr. Golan said...
就像格兰医生说的
maybe I can move on.
也许我就能放下了
Like, closure.
就像一种了结
Having an opportunity to see this children's home...
有机会去看看这个福利院
and separate fantasy from reality...
将现实和幻想分离开
may be helpful.
也许会有用
And at the very least...
至少
a trip like this provides a chance to...
这样一次旅行能让杰克有机会
say goodbye.
说再见
"Cairnholm. Population of 92.
“卡瑞霍姆，人口92人
"Best known for its proximity...
“因其最接近
"to the final resting place of the cruise liner Augusta...
“奥古斯塔号邮轮最后的安息地而为人所知
"which sank in 1915.
“奥古斯塔号于1915年沉没
"There is just one hotel..."
“岛上只有一家旅馆”
That's us.
只能住那儿了
Yeah. I hope there's bourbon.
希望那里有波本酒
Jake, check it out.
杰克！快看
That's a peregrine falcon.
是只游隼
A peregrine, like the headmistress?
游隼，和那个女校长的名字一样
Sure.
是啊
That's probably where Grandpa came up
说不定这就是为什么爷爷提到
with that whole turning into a bird thing.
变成鸟的事情
Or maybe, maybe that's really her!
说不定那真的是她
Hey, Miss Peregrine.
佩小姐！
It's me, Jake.
我是杰克
I'm Abe Portman's grandson.
亚伯·波特曼的孙子
Please don't crap on us.
拜托别在我们头上拉便便
Oh, my God. Dad, I'm kidding.
爸，我开玩笑呢！
What the... Hello?
这…有人吗？
Hello?
有人吗？
Anybody home?
有人在吗？
Oh, hey.
你好
Any idea where I'd find the manager of this place?
你知道这里的经理在哪儿吗？
That's me. Sorry to keep you.
是我，抱歉久等了
Just helping Uncle Oggie to the loo.
刚带奥吉叔去上厕所了
I'm Kev. There's room upstairs.
我是凯文，楼上有房间
Oh, great.
太好了
I'll be back in a bit.
我很快回来
Kev's just getting our suite ready.
凯文去帮我们准备房间了
Um, while we're waiting...
还要等一会儿
I thought maybe we could go check out the beach.
要不咱们去海滩看看？
I thought we would go to the children's home.
我还以为咱们要去儿童福利院呢
Is the beach where the birds nest?
那些鸟是在海滩上筑巢吗？
I thought we could just check it out real quick.
我们…可以很快看一眼
I could go to the home by myself.
我可以自己去福利院
Then, you can really take your time and enjoy it.
你就不用太匆忙了
Come on, Jakey. You know your mom would freak.
别这样，小杰，你妈知道了肯定会抓狂的
What if we can find someone to take me?
要不找个人带我去吧
Hey, dudes.
嗨，各位
- Dad. Don't. - Shh! I got this.
- 爸！别！ - 别吵
I was just wondering if any of you guys...
你们谁
might be interested in taking my son here
有兴趣带我儿子
to the other side of the island.
去岛的另一边吗？
So, what are your names?
你俩叫什么啊？
I'm Worm. This is MC Dirty D.
我是虫子，他是D哥
MC Dirty Bizniz.
坏小子D哥
I thought you changed it.
我还以为你改了？
No.
没有
No, you did, remember?
你不记得了？
When Ruth said "MC Dirty Bizniz"
露丝说坏小子D哥
made it sound like you cacked your trousers.
听起来好像你裤子破了似的
Yeah, but she said "Dirty D" sounded like
对，但她说这个名字听起来
a personal hygiene problem.
好像个人卫生有问题
Wait. Are these, like, nicknames, or...
听起来像是外号…
Stage names. We're the sickest rappers in Wales.
是艺名，我俩是威尔士最屌的说唱歌手
Go on, Worm. Show this Yank how it's done.
快，虫子，给美国佬露两手
What? Now?
现在？
I like to get wrecked down the Priest Hole
我要把教堂搅个地覆天翻
Your dad's always here 'cause he's on the dole
因为你爸去教堂领救济的钱
Our rhymes are tight Yet I make it look easy
我们的韵脚最屌但听起来好像不难
Our beats are hot like chicken jalfrezi
我们的节奏最炫好像火爆的咖喱饭
Oh, yeah, no. It's good.
挺好的
Should we take the shortcut, D?
咱们抄小道吧，D哥
We'll get there quicker. Take it from me.
这样快一点，从这儿走
What, down here?
这里下去？
Go.
去吧
This way?
这边？
What the...
这…
Is this even the way to the children's home?
这是去福利院的路吗？
Right through those trees.
要穿过那片林子
No use crying over a lost shoe, boy-o.
鞋丢了就丢了吧，孩子
The children's home. What happened to it?
那个福利院…发生了什么事？
A German air raid. Bomb fell right on the roof.
德军空袭，炸弹正好落到福利院屋顶
September the 3rd, 1943.
1943年9月3号
Where did they go after?
那…之后那些孩子呢？
The headmistress and the children.
女校长和孩子们呢？
Not one survivor. Poor little buggers.
无人生还，可怜的小东西们
And they were lovely, too.
都还那么可爱
Why didn't he tell us that they all died?
为什么爷爷不告诉我们他们都死了？
He leaves to join the army, and 3 months later,
他离家去参军，三个月后
everyone he knows gets killed?
他认识的人都死了
Not even Grandpa could turn that into a bedtime story.
就算是爷爷也没法把这编成晚安故事啊
Well, no wonder he was scared of being a dad...
也难怪他害怕做爸爸
being close to anyone.
和别人亲近
Listen.
听我说
You need to talk about all this with someone, buddy.
你应该找人谈谈这件事
We should call Dr. Golan.
我们可以给格兰医生打电话
Certainly some enjoyment today.
真是个好天气
Er, do you mind if I go hang out
我可以跟
with those other kids today?
其他孩子一起玩吗？
They asked.
他们叫我一起玩
Yeah? That's awesome.
当然了，很棒啊
Abe?
亚伯？
No!
不！
You're Emma!
你是艾玛
And the twins.
还有双胞胎
And Olive.
奥利弗
And Bronwyn.
布朗温
And he's Millard.
他是米拉德
No, you're dead.
不对啊，你死了
All of you, you're all dead.
你们都死了
He's invisible, but he's still dead.
他虽然能隐形，但是也死了
None of us are dead.
我们都没死
Oh, my God. Am I dead?
天呐，难道是我死了？
No.
不是
You called me Abe.
刚才在里面
In the house. Why?
你为什么叫我亚伯？
You looked like him.
你跟他很像
Just for a moment,
一瞬间很像而已
before you started screaming...
后来你就又喊又叫
running away, and concussing yourself.
跑掉了，还撞到了脑袋
Wait. What's happening?
这是怎么回事？
We're waiting until the coast is clear...
我们在等天黑
before we go into the loop.
然后去圈里
You never know who might be watching.
隔墙有耳，不可不防
Wait. Before we go into what?
你刚说去哪里
Please, Jake.
快走吧，杰克
Miss Peregrine's waiting. She saw you on the ferry.
佩小姐在等你，她看见你们的船了
She sent us to get you.
她派我们来接你
Hey!
嘿！
Where do you think you're going?
你准备去哪里啊？
To my room.
回房间啊
I'm a guest here.
我是这里的住客
Does this look like a hotel to you?
你看这像旅馆吗？
Yeah.
对啊
No. I've got a key.
我有钥匙
Talk to the manager. He'll tell you.
你问问经理，他知道
I'm the manager, boy.
我就是经理
He's American. Maybe he's army?
他是美国人，可能是军人
Bollocks.
胡说
Listen to his accent. It's terrible.
听他的口音，真难听
He's a spy.
他是个间谍
What?
什么？
No, I'm not. I'm a tourist.
我不是，我是游客
I say we should get the truth out of him
要我说，我们让他说实话
the old-fashioned way.
按老规矩来
Come on!
快走！
Jake, get on!
杰克，快上来！
Come on! Get on, boy!
快点！
I can't believe you're real. You're all real!
原来你们都是真的！
We have been trying to tell you.
不是一直在告诉你嘛
But I'm special, too.
但是原来我也很特殊
What?
什么？
in the pub. Olive, you saw.
刚才在酒馆啊，奥利芙看见了
Right? Everything was flying and breaking.
那些东西飞来飞去的
And that was me!
是我干的
I was doing it with my mind.
用意念
Millard?
米拉德？
Yeah.
对啊
Are you naked?
你没穿衣服？
Oh.
哦
I don't...
我不…
A bomb dropped on you in 1943.
1943年一颗炸弹落在你们头顶
It is 1943.
现在就是1943年
September the 3rd, 1943.
1943年9月3日
All day, every day.
每一天，这一天
It's our loop.
就是我们的圈
Right on time.
分秒不差
Miss Peregrine. Delighted to meet you.
我是佩小姐，幸会幸会
I do hope I'm not going to have the pub landlord
希望酒馆老板不会再
knocking on my door with the police again.
带着警察找上门来了
I've had to kill them twice this month.
这个月已经杀过他们两次了
It's been terribly inconvenient.
太不方便了
Millard broke a few things. That's all.
米拉德打破了几件东西，再没了
And Olive may have started a tiny fire.
还有奥利芙好像放了点火
But they were going to hurt Jake.
但是他们要伤害杰克的
Look at you.
瞧瞧你
The last time dear Abe sent me a photograph...
亚伯上一次寄给我的照片上
you were just a tiny tot.
你还是个小宝宝呢
Don't just stand there. Come in.
别站着了，快进来吧
Your tea's getting cold.
茶都要凉了
How did you know about the pub?
你怎么知道酒馆的事？
You weigh approximately 109 pounds, correct?
你体重大概109磅，对吧？
I don't...
我不…
Bronwyn and the twins returned 6 minutes after you ran away.
你跑掉后6分钟布朗温和双胞胎就回来了
I think I'm missing something.
我可能漏掉了什么
And quite apart from the fact
你觉得酒馆是安全的
that the perceived safety of the pub...
所以最可能的情况就是你
makes it the most likely place to which you would flee...
一路跑回了酒馆
it would take you 18 minutes to run there.
跑回酒馆要花18分钟时间
Emma and Millard would have been moments behind...
艾玛和米拉德坐马车过去
on the horse and trap,
会稍晚一点
traveling at 8.2 miles per hour.
他们的速度是8.2英里每小时
Factoring in some sort of kerfuffle at the pub...
考虑到酒馆里发生的混乱
and the return journey with your added weight...
和返程中增加了你的重量
you would arrive here at 13 minutes past 4.
你们会在4点过13分准时到达
Now, then, do you take sugar?
好了，你的茶要加糖吗？
That'll do. Thank you, Olive.
可以了，谢谢你，奥利芙
Nobody enjoys over-boiled tea.
茶太烫了可不好
Let me help you with those, Enoch.
我来帮你吧，伊诺克
Don't bother. Wouldn't want to interrupt your tea party.
不麻烦了，我可不想搅了你们的雅兴
I'm so sorry for your loss, Jake.
节哀顺变，杰克
You know, then.
看来你知道了
I know if Abe were alive,
我知道如果亚伯活着
he would have told me you were coming.
一定会通知我们你要来
Shall we take our tea outside?
我们到外面喝茶吧
Thank you.
谢谢
Before he died, he told me to find you.
他死之前，让我找到你
There was something he wanted me to know.
有些事他想让我知道
He said you could explain everything.
他说你会向我解释所有事
That's absolutely true.
确实如此
There are very few things I can't explain.
少有我解释不了的事情
We're what's known, in common parlance,
我们就是通用语中所说的
as "peculiar."
“异能”
51 seconds late, Fiona.
晚了51秒，菲奥娜
Sorry, Miss Peregrine.
对不起，佩小姐
How many carrots do you need for supper?
晚餐需要准备多少胡萝卜？
Just one will do.
一颗就够了
As I was saying, some people are peculiar.
刚才说到，有些人拥有异能
It's a recessive gene carried down through families.
是家族中遗传下来的隐性基因
Yet, many generations can pass
然而，很多家庭的很多代人中
without a peculiar child being born.
都很难出现一个异能的孩子
And alas, peculiars have been persecuted through the ages.
因此，异能人很多年来一直受到迫害
Hence, we live in places like this.
所以我能才生活在这样的地方
In Wales?
威尔士？
Anywhere will do if you pick the right day.
只要选对了日子，哪里都是一样
That's fine now, Fiona.
这就可以了，菲奥娜
You see, I'm a type of peculiar called an Ymbryne.
我的异能是我是只回时鸟
That means I can...
也就是说我可以
Yeah, you turn into a bird.
对，你可以变成鸟
I do. Yes.
话是没错
But that's not very useful.
不过这没多大用处
An Ymbryne's main skill is the manipulation of time.
回时鸟的主要能力是可以操控时间
We choose a safe place, a safe day...
我们挑个安全的日子，安全的地点
and create a loop.
然后创造圈
What do you mean?
这是什么意思？
A loop preserves the last 24 hours.
一个时间圈可以保持24小时
Reset the loop, and the day is yours to live in again.
重置时间圈，就可以重新生活这一天
Reset it daily...
每天重置
and you can stay there forever.
就可以永远停留
Entirely safe from the outside world.
与世隔绝，保证安全
Right on time, Bronwyn. Good girl.
刚刚好，布朗温，好姑娘
And that's why we Ymbrynes
所以总是由回时鸟
are charged with the care of the young.
来照顾孩子们
And no one ever gets older.
没有人会老去
It's best for everyone this way.
这是最好的方法
I assure you.
我向你保证
Every Ymbryne commits herself...
每一只回时鸟都会…
to the creation and upkeep of a place like this.
创造和守护一个这样的地方
A home for peculiar children.
这是异能孩子的家园
You met the twins.
你已经见过双胞胎了
This is Claire.
这是克莱尔
Millard you met.
你也见过米拉德了
And that's Hugh.
那是休
Stop cheating, Hugh.
休，不要作弊
Millard, that's a foul again.
米勒，你又犯规了！
No, it wasn't. Ref?
才不是！裁判？
If you two can't play soccer without squabbling...
如果你们玩的时候非要吵架
I do wish you wouldn't play at all.
那就最好不要玩
Do you know what a referee is?
你知道裁判是干什么的吗？
Good afternoon. I'm Horace.
下午好，我是霍勒斯
Delighted to meet you.
很高兴见到你
We sorely need some new blood here.
我们急需新鲜血液的注入
Super shirt, by the way.
衬衣不错
Thanks.
谢了
You know Emma, of course.
你肯定知道艾玛
And I think that's everyone.
差不多人都认齐了
Didn't Bronwyn have a brother?
布朗温是不是有个兄弟？
Yes. Victor's upstairs.
对，维克多在楼上
Wait, where did Enoch and Olive go?
等等，伊诺克和奥莉芙去哪儿了？
Heaven knows.
鬼知道
Enoch's been off sulking ever since we went out to get Jake.
从我们去找杰克时，伊诺克就不见了
Miss Peregrine, there's a policeman at the door.
佩小姐，有个警察在敲门
He says it's about the pub!
他说来处理酒馆的事
We'll discuss this later, Emma.
我们等会再谈这事，艾玛
It wasn't their fault.
不是他们的错
Honestly, they were just trying to help.
真的，他们只是想要帮我
Thanks.
谢谢
You're not as wet as I thought.
你没我想的那么傻
She's not really gonna kill anyone, is she?
她不会杀人的，对吧？
Not if she can talk her way out of it.
只要她能说服那个人
Would you help me with something?
帮我个忙吧
Enoch usually does it, but like I said,
通常都是伊诺克干的
he's off sulking somewhere.
不过他现在应该在哪儿生闷气呢
Is that because of me?
是因为我吗？
He's possessive.
他占有欲很强
So, what did you need help with?
所以…你要我帮你什么？
One of my daily chores.
我的一项日常工作
Put the baby squirrel back in the tree.
把松鼠宝宝送回树上
What baby squirrel?
什么松鼠宝宝？
That happens every day?
每天都会发生？
Like clockwork.
分秒不差
Now, would you mind tying that rope around my waist?
能帮我把绳子拴在腰上吗？
Right. Promise to hold on tight.
一定要抓紧绳子啊
I nearly messed that up.
差点搞砸了
Abe did, too, the first time.
亚伯也是…第一次的时候
This used to be his job.
这以前是他的工作
Emma, I need to tell you something.
艾玛，我得告诉你件事
He's dead.
他死了
I know.
我知道
Miss Peregrine guessed, and she's always right.
佩小姐猜到了，她总是对的
It's okay.
没事的
I said goodbye to him a long time ago.
我很久以前就和他说过再见了
Were you close?
你们很亲近是吗？
I thought we were.
我以为是
For a while.
一度
But I suppose not.
但我觉得应该不是
Can I ask, was he like you?
容我问一句，他喜欢你，对吧？
He was like you, Jake.
他很像你，杰克
I need to go and change for supper.
我要去换件衣服，准备吃晚餐了
Will you be dining with us?
你会和我们一起用餐吗？
I can't stay out late.
我不能在外面待太晚
Supper's at 5:30.
晚餐五点半开始
Uh... That is pretty early.
那…挺早的
The fact we're not all eight years old
幸好我们不都是八岁的孩子
seems to have eluded Miss Peregrine.
给佩小姐减少了不少负担
You can borrow some of Abe's clothes.
你可以借件亚伯的衣服穿
His room's in the attic.
他的房间在阁楼
Jake!
杰克
Come and meet Enoch properly.
来认识认识伊诺克
You must feel pretty out of place.
你应该不太适应这里的环境
Don't worry.
不用担心
I'm used to it.
我习惯了
No. I wasn't worried.
我不担心
Some advice for you though, man to man.
但还是给你一些忠告，开诚布公的讲
If you're thinking of staying just because you like Emma...
如果你只是因为喜欢艾玛才待在这里
don't bother.
就不必了
You see, she swore off romance decades ago...
她心碎以后
when she got her heart broken.
已经多年不沾情爱了
And she's never gonna change her mind. So...
她也不会改变想法的
Enoch, I wasn't...
伊诺克，我不是…
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Isn't he amazing?
是不是很棒？
What did you do?
你刚才做的是什么？
This?
这个？
Jake, this isn't even the fun part.
杰克，这还不是最有趣的
Do you want to see the fun part?
你想看最有趣的吗？
They're like puppets.
它们就像傀儡
Just do anything I tell them.
听我的命令
It's even more fun with people.
如果是人的话就更有趣了
You should have seen some of
你该看看我以前参与的
the epic battles they used to have...
史诗级的战争
at my parents' funeral parlor.
发生在我父母的葬礼上
You'll need a necktie.
你还需要领结
So what did my grandpa do when he was traveling?
我祖父在旅行期间，做了什么？
Visited other loops.
参观其他的时间圈
Really? To do what?
是吗？做什么？
Jake, there's some questions
杰克，有些问题
that I can't answer, all right?
我不能回答你的，好吗？
So, it would be a lot easier for me if you just...
所以你最好还是
stopped asking them.
不要问了
Hey! What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Millard.
米拉德
Go and put some clothes on.
去穿件衣服
Polite persons do not take their supper in the nude.
懂礼貌的人不会吃晚餐的时候不穿衣服
All right. All right.
好吧！
You can sit here, Jake.
杰克你可以坐这里
Look at Enoch.
瞧瞧伊诺克
He's jealous.
他又嫉妒了
Why would I be jealous?
我嫉妒什么？
Olive can go marry Jake, for all I care.
你们想结婚就结好了，与我无关
Don't be mean, Enoch. She doesn't want to.
伊诺克，别这样，她没这样想
She's just excited to have a visitor.
她只是因为有访客而激动罢了
Nobody is marrying anybody.
没人要结婚
Now, eat up your food before it gets cold.
现在大家快吃饭，别等菜凉了
Hugh!
休
Where's your net?
你的网罩呢？
Hugh! You have to stop doing this, Hugh.
休，别这样！
Must be very strange for you, Jake.
杰克，你一定觉得十分诡异吧
Meeting your grandfather's friends.
见到了你祖父的朋友
Visiting another century.
来到另一个世纪
Are there spaceships in your time, Jake?
你生活的时代有宇宙飞船吗？
Like the Flash Gordon books.
像飞侠哥顿里的一样
Now, now, Olive.
好了！奥莉芙
What did I say about asking questions?
我以前说过什么
We don't discuss the future here.
我们不讨论将来
We enjoy living in the good old here and now.
只活在当下，享受一切
Claire, why aren't you eating?
克莱尔，你怎么不吃?
She's embarrassed in front of Jake.
在杰克面前，她不太好意思
Don't be. Please.
没关系的
So, Jake, what's your peculiarity?
杰克，你的异能是什么？
Oh, I'm not peculiar.
我…我没有异能
And that, my friends,
看到了吧
is why he will not be staying with us...
这就是他为什么不能和我们待在一起
no matter how hard we try to persuade him.
不管我们怎么劝他
We've spoken about this. Jake is just visiting.
我们已经说过这件事了，杰克只是来做客的
He might want to stay.
他也许想留下呢
Don't you want to stay, Jake?
你想待在这里吗，杰克？
Tonight? Or...
今晚还是…
Forever. You should stay forever.
永远，你应该永远留在这里
Why would he, if he doesn't have to?
没必要的话为什么要留下来？
He can live out there, grow older...
他可以在外面生活，慢慢变老
have a good time instead.
享受时光
He'll leave, just like his grandfather did.
然后像他祖父那样，离开人世
Emma!
艾玛！
Excuse me.
抱歉
Where's she going?
她去哪里？
That wasn't nice, Enoch.
伊诺克，这样很不好！
You know perfectly well why Abe left us.
你明明知道亚伯离开我们
To join the army.
是为了去参军
And then he met a lady, and had a nice wedding cake...
接着他遇到了一个姑娘，然后结了婚
and a lovely little baby.
还有个可爱的小宝宝
Children.
孩子们！
I know you'd all like a new friend...
我知道你们都想认识新朋友
but I'm sure Jake has plenty of his own back in Florida.
但杰克在佛罗里达还有很多自己的事
I think you should all get ready
我希望在我接完电话后
for movie time while I answer that.
你们可以准备好去看电影了
But you always let us stay for it.
可是你总是让我们待在那里
Hello, this is Abe.
嗨，我是亚伯
How is everyone?
大家都还好吗？
Yours has extra marshmallows, Jake.
杰克，你的我多加了棉花糖糖
Millard, put some pajamas on.
米拉德，把睡衣穿上
It's too hot in here.
这里好热
Stop moaning.
不要抱怨了
Excuse me.
抱歉
My grandpa told me about this.
我祖父给我讲过
Horace projects his dreams, right?
霍勒斯能把他做的梦投放出来，是吗？
He used to listen to the radio.
他过去常听收音机
Gets tedious when you know every word off by heart.
极其乏味，我已经倒背如流了
Splendid. I'll take it.
很好，这件我要了
He dreams about clothes mostly.
很多都是关于服装的
Delighted to meet you.
很高兴见到你
Super shirt, by the way.
衬衫不错
When did he dream this?
他什么时候梦到这个的？
Last night.
昨晚
Some of his dreams are prophetic.
有些梦有预见性
But, mostly they're about clothes.
但绝大多数还是关于服装的
Prophetic as in, he can see into the future?
预见性是说，他能预见未来？
An Ymbryne. Who is she?
回时鸟，她是谁？
Miss Peregrine, do you know her?
佩小姐，你认识她吗？
Don't be silly.
傻瓜
Horace must have just had a bad dream. That's all.
霍勒斯只是做了个噩梦而已
That's quite enough of that. Thank you, Horace.
足够了，谢谢你，霍勒斯
I should probably get going.
我想我该走了
You could stay the night, if you wanted to.
你可以在这待一晚上，你愿意的话
Rather than walk home alone in the dark.
这样就不要晚上走回去了
But the island is very safe, isn't it?
这座岛不是挺安全的吗？
Of course!
当然
I only meant the path is dreadfully bumpy.
我是说这里的路特别难走
Jake could trip.
杰克可能会跌倒
Perhaps you could show him the shortcuts.
或许你可以带他走近路？
Should he ever need to avoid bumps.
这样他就不会跌倒了
Won't you at least stay to see the reset, Jake?
不留下来看看如何开始新的一天吗？
It's really quite spectacular.
超震撼的
Yeah! Stay, Jake!
留下来吧，杰克！
What was that?
什么声音？
It was my phone.
我的手机
It's been dead the whole time in the loop. I guess now...
可能是在时间圈里，一直都没信号
Your phone?
你的手机？
Yeah. Like a telephone.
对，就像电话
You can call people...
可以打电话
send written messages.
可以发短信
Wait, you'll love this.
对了，你会喜欢这个的
You can take a picture.
你可以拍照
Press that, there. Yeah.
按那里…那…对
See?
看见了没？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
It's just funny to think that one day, you'll grow up.
想到有一天你会长大
Like Abe did.
就像亚伯
Get married, have children.
结婚生子
Grandchildren.
孙子孙女
You might even show them this photograph.
你也许还会给他们看这张照片
And I'll still be here.
而我还在这里
Couldn't you leave some day?
你能离开这里吗？
And live in the present, if you wanted to?
如果你想的话，能生活在现实世界吗？
No.
不行
More than a few minutes in your time
在那里待几分钟
and the years would catch up.
时间就会赶上来
You would age?
你会变老？
I think it's the Ymbryne from Horace's dream.
这个好像是霍勒斯梦中的回时鸟
Are you sure it's not just a bird?
你确定它不是一只普通的鸟吗？
I don't know, wouldn't it change?
我不知道，它难道不会变身吗？
She can't. Not if she's hurt.
不能，她受伤了
I need to take her inside. You should go.
我要把她带进去，你该走了
Please don't say anything else.
请不要说话了
I hate goodbyes.
我讨厌说再见
I'll come back tomorrow.
我明天再来
There's no hurry. I'll be here forever.
不用着急，我永远都在这里
Hey!
嘿！
I've been all over this damn island.
我在这个破岛上转了一整天了
Where the hell were you?
你去哪儿了？
Um, I was just on my way back.
我正好往回走
I'm sorry. I lost track of time.
对不起，我忘了看时间了
I was having a blast with Worm and Dirty D.
我和虫子，还有D哥玩儿了一天
Dirty D?
D哥？
You know what?
你知道吗？
This is good. This is healthy.
我觉得这样挺好，很健康
You're making weird friends...
你认识了古怪的朋友
and doing teenage stuff.
跟其他年轻人们一样
I think this is normal.
我觉得这挺好的
I'm sure Doctor Golan will approve.
格兰医生肯定会同意这么做的
Hey, you. American!
嘿，那个美国佬
Get over here.
到这儿来
Oh, look. There they are.
哦，他们俩在那儿
There's D-Bag and Worm Man.
D哥和虫子
Did you do this?
是你干的吗？
What? No.
什么？不是！
Of course not.
当然不是
It wasn't us.
肯定不是我们
Listen, sir. I don't know what happened here.
这位先生，我不知道这里发生了什么
But my son and his friends have been together all day.
但是我儿子一直和他朋友在一起
Jake would never do anything like this.
杰克肯定不会干这种事儿的
Bollocks! We haven't seen him!
胡说！我们今天就没见过他！
You paid us yesterday.
你昨天付了我们钱
Why would we hang out with him today for free?
我们今天为什么要免费陪他玩儿？
Jake? Were you with them or not?
杰克，你今天有没有和他们在一起？
No. I'm sorry.
没有！对不起！
But you don't seriously think I could do this?
你不是真的觉得这是我做的吧？
I think we're done here, sir.
我想我们已经都弄清楚了
Can you pass on a message for me?
能帮我留个言吗？
Can you tell Doctor Golan...
你就告诉格兰医生
that if she hadn't encouraged this cockamamie trip...
要不是她怂恿进行这次荒谬的旅行
maybe my son wouldn't be
我儿子也不会
moping around all day in a derelict house...
跑到一个废弃的房子里面呆了一整天
having a goddamn breakdown!
以至于都神情恍惚了！
Hello?
喂？
Dad, I'm not.
爸，我没有
I'm fine.
我没事儿
No. You're not.
你不好
You're not fine, Jake.
你有事儿，杰克
Coming here was a terrible, terrible idea.
到这儿来就是个彻头彻尾的错误
Look, I'm sorry I lied. I just wanted...
对不起，我说谎了
Just set your alarm for 8:00 a.m.
闹钟定在早上8点
I wanna get to the beach early.
我想早点儿去海滩上看看
The rest of the time we're stuck
剩下这几天
on this craphole island...
在这个破岛上
we're sticking together.
我们俩必须一起行动
Where are you going?
你去哪儿？
Downstairs for a drink.
去楼下喝一杯
Dear Miss Peregrine...
亲爱的佩小姐
I don't wish to alarm you...
我不想让你们担心
but one of my informants sent me this.
但是我的一个线人告诉我
It would appear that some of Mr. Barron's group...
巴伦先生的一些同伙
are in Blackpool, England.
出现在英格兰黑谭镇附近
If I recall...
如果我没记错
Miss Avocet has a loop there.
艾娃塞小姐在那儿有一个时间圈
Please warn her and suggest...
请给她发出预警
that she make a new one right away...
让她尽快建立一个新的时空循环
well-hidden.
隐匿好行踪
And take the greatest care yourself.
请珍重
With love, Abe.
祝好，亚伯
January, 2016.
2016年1月
Who's ready to hit the beach?
准备好去海滩了吗？
Oh, my...
我去…
Unbelievable.
难以置信！
Right in the middle of a nesting area?
在鸟巢区域架设备？
What kind of idiot does that?
哪儿来的外行居然这么干？
Actually, the main nesting area is over there.
事实上，主要筑巢区在那边
I can show you if you'd like.
你想看看吗，我可以领你过去
It's marvelous to meet a fellow bird spotter.
很高兴能在此遇到一个同样喜欢拍摄鸟类的人
John Lamont.
约翰·拉蒙特
Franklin Portman. This is my son, Jake.
富兰克林·波特曼，这是我儿子，杰克
That's a hell of a camera you got there.
你居然带着这么棒的相机来这儿
Oh, thanks. It's absolutely fantastic.
谢谢，这地方真是太赞了
I'm here to do some snaps for a book I'm writing.
我是来给我的书拍一些插图的
So, you gentlemen here on holiday?
你们二位是过来度假的吗？
Unfortunately, her wings were flapping
不幸的是，她的翅膀
as much as the bird's!
呼哒的就像一只鸟！
I think you fellas are
我觉得你们
thinking of another kind of bird.
现在想的是另一种鸟
So, you're not going to the beach today?
你今天不再去海滩照相了吗？
What's the point?
有什么意义呢？
If that guy is gonna cover Cairnholm
如果那个家伙举着相机
in some big, glossy book...
把整个岛的照片都发表在他那个包装精美的书里
no one's gonna even wanna look at mine.
谁还会看我拍的照片
Might just have a nice afternoon nap.
我去睡个午觉
I don't suppose you saw Uncle Oggie
你俩今早在哪里
on your travels this morning, did you?
看见老欧吉了吗？
He's usually here by now.
按说他现在应该过来了
I could go look for him.
我可以帮忙去找找他
You're not going anywhere.
你哪儿也别想去
Jake, you're back! Come and play!
杰克，你回来了！快来和我们一起玩儿！
I need to see Miss Peregrine first.
我想要先见见佩小姐
Do you know where she is?
你知道她在哪儿吗？
Jake. You're back. How wonderful!
杰克，你回来了，太好了！
How's it doing?
它怎么样了？
Emma said it was an Ymbryne.
艾玛说这是一只回时鸟
"She." Not "it."
她，不是“它”
Ymbrynes are always female.
回时鸟都是女性
And Emma was quite correct.
艾玛说的非常正确
This is Miss Avocet.
这位是艾娃塞小姐
Her loop's in Blackpool. England.
她的时间圈在英格兰黑谭镇
That was a private letter, Jake.
这是私人信件，杰克
Who is Mr. Barron?
谁是巴伦先生？
Miss Peregrine, if my Grandpa
佩小姐，如果我爷爷
was involved with dangerous people...
和什么危险的人物有瓜葛
I need to tell the police.
我有必要将这些都告诉给警察
Police?
告诉警察？
Are you implying Abe died an unnatural death?
你这是在暗示亚伯是非正常死亡吗？
I found him in the woods...
我在树林里找到他时
with his eyes missing.
他的眼睛不见了
I'd say that was pretty unnatural.
我觉得这很不正常
Unless essential, I don't discuss unpleasant matters.
除非必要，我不想讨论这些让人不愉快的事儿
An Ymbryne's duty is to protect children, Jake.
回时鸟的职责是保护孩子，杰克
I'm not a child.
我不是小孩儿了
He wanted you to tell me everything!
爷爷他想让你把这些都告诉我
Oh. How frustrating for you.
哦，真郁闷啊
Between Miss Peregrine's rules...
鉴于佩小姐的规定
and my housemates' little pact not to scare you off...
以及我那条不想吓坏你的室友守则
it's like no one's telling you anything!
所以，没有人会给你答案的
Why don't you, then?
要不你来告诉我？
It's not like you want me here.
反正你也不想我留在这儿
Enoch, you can't. You promised.
伊诺克，你不能告诉他，你保证过不说的
Olive's right.
奥利芙说得对
I do know someone who can get away
但是我知道有一个人
with breaking rules though.
可以不用遵守这项规定
Want to meet him?
你想去见见他吗？
Enoch, don't do this. Please!
伊诺克，别这么做，求你了！
You want to spend time with me and Jake,
是你想大家一起玩的
we can all play together.
我们可以一起玩
That's what you said.
自己说的话不记得了？
Here we all are.
就是这儿了
Move, Olive.
让开，奥利芙
If you're going to be like that,
你要是非这么做
then I don't want to be your friend.
我以后就不跟你做朋友了
Enoch, leave Victor alone. It really upsets Bronwyn.
伊诺克！别打扰维克多，布朗温会不高兴的
Stop fussing, Fiona.
别闹了，菲奥娜
Don't you think Jake should meet everybody?
你不觉得杰克应该和这里的每个人都认识一下吗？
He's trying to frighten you away, Jake.
他想把你吓跑，杰克
He was always jealous of Abe. And now he's jealous of you.
他一直都嫉妒艾伯，现在他又开始嫉妒你
Come and play with us instead.
还是过来跟我们一起玩儿吧
I'd quite like to meet Victor.
我想我应该去见见维克多
After you.
你先请
Hello, Victor.
你好维克多
I'm Jake. I'm sorry to disturb...
我是杰克，不好意思打扰你
Yeah, he can't hear you.
他听不见你说话
Hello, Jake. I'm Victor.
你好杰克，我叫维克多
Do you want to know what killed me?
你想知道是什么杀害了我吗？
There you are. Is Enoch with you?
你在这儿呢，他没和你一起吗？
It's time for our daily walk.
到了每天散步的时间了
Emma, who killed Victor?
艾玛，是谁害了维克多？
Was it the people with the white eyes?
是那些白色眼睛的人吗？
I asked you not to ask questions.
我跟你说了别问这么多
I saw one the night my grandpa died.
我爷爷去世的那晚我见过一个
A man.
这样的人
If it really was one,
如果你的确见过这么一个
you have to tell Miss Peregrine.
你应该告诉佩小姐
Could you recognize him from a photograph?
你能从照片里认出这个人吗？
Do you have one?
你有照片吗？
Come on. There's somewhere I go to be alone.
那就跟我走，跟我去个地儿
I have things there.
我在那儿存了些东西
Is this the place?
是这儿吗？
No. This is how we get there.
不是，这只是我们去哪儿的途径
Oh! Emma! Your shoes!
艾玛！你的鞋！
Lead shoes!
铅鞋！
Welcome to my secret hideout.
欢迎来到我的秘密基地
How did you...
你是，你是怎么？
Air.
空气
It's my peculiarity.
这是我的能力
It does what I want.
它可以帮我实现想法
Jake...
杰克
before your grandfather retired...
你爷爷退隐前
he asked me to keep this safe.
让我保管这些
This is my grandpa's old map.
这些是我爷爷的旧地图
It shows you where the loops are.
上面标记了时间圈的所在地
That's him!
就是他
That's the man I saw.
这就是我见过的那个人
Who is he? That's Barron.
他是谁？这就是巴伦
He's the leader.
他是领头人
The leader of what?
什么的领头人？
Who are these people?
这些人都是谁？
Bad people. Bad peculiars.
坏人，坏的异能者
Abe dedicated his life to hunting them down.
亚伯终其一生都在追捕这些人
These are the ones he never found.
这些是他没有找到的
What do you mean, hunting?
“追捕”是什么意思？
They raided loops.
他们会袭击时间圈
Whole homes full of children left for dead.
残忍的杀害其中所有的孩子
Abe took lives to save lives.
亚伯只是以暴制暴
He only retired when you were born to protect you.
你出生后，为了保护你他就退隐了
From what?
保护我什么？
If I tell you the rest,
如果我告诉你全部
you have to promise not to run away.
你要保证你不逃避
Jake, you belong here.
杰克，你是属于这里的
You know I don't.
你知道我不属于
I'm not like you.
我和你不一样
I'm just ordinary.
我是个普通人
No, you're not.
不，你不是
Jake...
杰克
only a peculiar can enter a time loop.
只有异能人才能进入时间圈
No. That can't be right.
不是，这不可能
I would know.
我是说，我要是异能人我应该知道
Fine.
好吧
Then I'll show you something else.
那么我就给你看看其他的
Hurry. You'll miss it.
快来！会赶不上的
Ymbrynes usually pick the perfect day to create a loop.
回时鸟通常会选择一个完美的日子去建立时间圈
But Miss Peregrine had to make this one in a rush.
但是佩小姐是匆忙间选择的日子
Why?
为什么？
Because the Germans were about to drop a bomb on the house.
因为德国人会用炸弹摧毁我们的房子
The point is...
问题是
September the 3rd, 1943 wasn't perfect.
1943年9月3日不是个完美的日子
The thing that killed Victor came back.
那个杀害了维克多的家伙那天又回来了
Wait! Watch out!
等等，小心！
You'll put her off!
你会让她分心的！
You can see it, can't you?
你能看见，是不是？
No one else can.
没有人能看得见
It's invisible, Jake.
他们是隐形的，杰克
That was Abe's greatest gift of all.
这就是亚伯的天赋
He could see the monsters.
他可以看见那些怪物
We call them Hollowgast.
我们管他们叫灵体变异人
Hollows for short.
简称灵人
My grandpa told me about people who turn into monsters.
我爷爷跟我提过有变成怪物的人
Is that what they are?
就是他们吗？
I will explain everything, Jake.
我会详细跟你解释的，杰克
I fear it's my duty now, considering.
考虑到现在的情况，我恐怕没得选
But you should know that in doing so,
但是你要知道
I'm breaking a solemn promise.
我这么做的确破坏了我曾经发过的誓
I knew you were peculiar when you were born.
你一出生我就知道你是异能人
But your grandfather forbid me to tell you anything.
但是你爷爷让我什么都不要告诉你
His dearest wish was for you to have an ordinary childhood.
他最大的愿望就是希望你能有一个正常的童年
I definitely had that.
我的童年的确过得很平凡
He intended to tell you the truth when you turned 18.
他本来打算等你18岁之后再告诉你的
He hoped his bedtime stories would pave the way.
他希望那些睡前故事可以提前铺垫一下
Here's my book.
这是我的书
Many years ago...
很多年前
a splinter faction emerged among our people.
从我们的族群中分裂出了一批人
Disaffected peculiars tired of living in loops.
对于异能人只能存在于时间圈中非常不满意
That's Mr. Barron.
这就是巴伦先生
He believed that by harnessing the essence
他认为按照他的方法
of an Ymbryne's powers...
提取回时鸟的能力
he and his cronies could gain immortality...
他和他的同伙可以获得永生
and be able to live outside loops.
而且不用困在时间圈里
He devised an experiment.
于是他就设计了一个试验
He kidnapped an Ymbryne...
他绑架了一只回时鸟
not knowing or caring
在不顾那只回时鸟死活的情况下
whether she would survive the experiment.
开始了试验
But the fate of Barron and his group
但是巴伦和他的同伙
was more horrifying still.
下场相当惨烈
Why didn't Barron turn into one?
为什么巴伦没什么变？
He did.
他变了
But years later...
可在这之后几年里
he found a way to reverse the effects.
他发现了可以逆转异常
To regain humanity.
变回人类的方法
They had become not immortal gods, but Hollows.
他们变的不老不死，但是以灵人的形式存在
Invisible beasts, dangerous...
危险冷血致命的
cold-blooded, deadly.
隐形怪物！
Remember I told you they raided loops?
记得我之前提过他们袭击时间圈吗？
This is why.
这就是原因
Barron discovered that by consuming
巴伦发现食用其他异能人
the eyes of other peculiars...
特别是儿童期的
especially children...
异能人的眼睛
he began to change.
可以令他恢复
Consume enough, and a Hollow
食用到足够多的眼睛，灵人就能
can fully regain its human form.
完全变回人形
Bon appetit.
祝各位好胃口
Just as Barron and some of his friends did.
只有巴伦和他的同伙能够复原
The rest of them are stuck as Hollows.
其他还是以灵人的形态存在
Are you saying that Barron ate my grand...
你是说巴伦吃了我爷爷的
He needs no more eyes himself.
他自己已经不需要吃眼睛来维持形态了
But I fear he led a Hollow to your grandfather. Yes.
恐怕是他指使灵人找到了你爷爷，吃了他的眼睛
After the first attacks on loops...
在他们第一次袭击了时间圈后
we all got better at hiding, making new loops,
我们也开始更加注意隐蔽，建立新的时间圈
keeping our whereabouts secret.
隐匿我们的行踪
The Hollows grow more desperate every year...
而那些灵人变得越来越贪婪
and Barron wishes to help his friends.
巴伦则希望能壮大自己的队伍
Miss Peregrine, come quickly. Miss Avocet's awake.
佩小姐！快来！艾娃塞小姐醒了
And suddenly, I flew into it again...
突然，我又飞了进去
Bang! Bang! I couldn't see anything.
什么都看不见
Oh, Miss Peregrine. They found my new loop.
佩小姐！他们发现了我新建的时间圈
The children. I tried to save them...
孩子们，我想尽一切办法试图救下她们
but there were so many Hollows.
但是灵人实在是太多了
I don't know how I escaped.
我都不记得我是怎么逃出来的
You're safe now.
你现在安全了
None of us are safe.
我们不可能安全的
They set up the machine in my loop.
他们在我的时间圈里面安了装置
They put it in the cellars at Blackpool Tower.
装置就在黑潭塔的地下室
They're still there.
那些人还在那儿
Their machine? The experiment.
装置？试验用的
They intend to do it again.
他们打算再做一次试验！
This time, he's using more Ymbrynes.
这次他将使用更多的回时鸟
He still wants to be immortal.
他还是想获得永生
Of course not.
当然不是！
They're monsters, Jake.
他们就是野兽，杰克
They'll slaughter anything in their path.
他们会将眼前的一切都屠杀殆尽
Some sheep on the island were killed.
岛上有些羊群被杀了
You don't think they're here already, do you?
他们不会已经到了这里吧？
Have you seen anyone with white eyes?
你有看到长着白色眼睛的人吗？
I'm sorry, children. We can't remain here.
孩子们，很抱歉，我们不能继续住在这儿了
What?
什么？
We'll leave on the first ferry off the island tomorrow.
我们乘坐明早第一班渡船离开这里
Pack anything of importance.
回去收拾行李
Then it's sandwiches and early to bed.
我去做些三明治然后哄你们上床睡觉
Are we leaving for good?
离开就再也不会来了吗？
When are we coming back? Never.
我们什么时候再回来？不会再回来了
If Miss Peregrine's not here
如果佩小姐明天晚上
to reset the loop tomorrow night...
不重置时间圈
the house gets bombed.
这房子就彻底被炸毁了
But our house.
什么？我们的房子？
Don't cry.
别哭
Miss Peregrine will find you
佩小姐会给你们
another lovely house, somewhere else.
重新找一座漂亮房子的
Once this loop closes, that's it.
一旦这个时间圈关闭
I can't get back to my own time.
我就再也不能回到自己的时空了
You didn't seem very happy there.
你在那里过得也不是很开心啊
I can't just leave! I have a family!
我不能就这么走了！我还有家人
And you felt ordinary.
你一直觉得自己平凡
Like, nothing you do changes anything!
觉得自己什么都不能改变
Now you have a chance to do something
现在你有一个机会
that changes everything!
可以拯救世界
Jake, we're in danger.
杰克，我们现在有危险
And you're the only one who can see the Hollows.
而你是我们中唯一一个可以看见灵人的
Yeah, see them, sure. But I'm not my grandpa!
是，我确实可以看见他们，但是我不是我爷爷
I'm not, and I can't fight.
我不是，我不知道怎么去战斗
I can't kill somebody.
我不会杀人
There's only one reason that I'd stay here...
只有一个理由可以让我留下来
Please.
别说了！
Just go.
你走吧
Jake? Jakey, there you are.
杰克，杰克原来你在这儿！
Thank God!
谢天谢地！
When I heard they found a body, I freaked.
听他们说找到了一具尸体时吓死我了
Are there stray dogs around here?
这儿也有流浪狗吗？
What you talking about?
你说什么？
It's like...
我是说
when they find an injured animal,
流浪狗发现受伤的动物后
they go for the soft parts first.
会先吃掉其中的软组织
Same thing happened to my father.
我父亲去世的时候也是这样
The police are on their way.
警察已经快到了
Look, Dad. I've gotta go.
爸爸，我得走了
What? No. You don't, Jake.
不行，你那儿也不能去，杰克
If this wasn't an accident,
如果这不是意外
there's a lunatic on the island.
那就是这个岛上有个疯子
I've known everyone on this island my whole life.
我认识这个岛上的每一个人
Except you, and him.
除了你和他
And he's been in the pub all afternoon.
而他在酒吧里坐了一下午
So have I. I was sleeping.
我也是，我一直都在睡觉
What about the blind fellow?
那个盲人呢？
I assumed he was blind.
我以为他也是个盲人
Gentleman with the dark glasses...
一个戴墨镜的先生
arrived on the same ferry as me?
是和我同一天坐渡轮一起过来的
I kept seeing him around.
我总能看见他在这附近
Jake!
杰克！
Jake! Wait!
杰克，等等！
Is your son all right?
你儿子还好吧？
No.
不好
He has mental health issues.
他有心理障碍
I can't go.
我追不上
Let me. I run 5-Ks all the time.
我帮你追，我经常会来个5公里跑
Hello?
你好！
Is that you, young man?
是你吗，年轻人？
You came through...
你能进入？
You're peculiar?
你是个异能人？
Oh, yes.
是的
And I'm extremely grateful to you.
真是多亏了你
Terribly hard to find loops these days.
这些日子想要找到时间圈越来越难了
So, you followed me from the beach on purpose?
你故意从海滩那儿一直尾随我？
Oh, no.
不不不
I've been following you much further than that.
我在很早以前就已经开始关注你了！
Doctor Golan?
格兰医生？
Sometimes.
有时候
When it suits me.
合适的时候
The breadth of my peculiarity...
一般来说能够局限我异能变化的
is purely limited by my imagination.
只有我的想象力
The only thing I can't change...
只有一样我没有办法改变
is my eyes.
就是我的眼睛
Mr. Barron. How do you do?
我是巴伦先生，你好吗？
I saw you at your grandfather's.
我在你爷爷家见过你
I was hoping to get
我本打算从他那儿
Miss Peregrine's address from him.
得到佩小姐的地址
But, alas, my traveling companion
但是和我一起过来的旅伴
got to him before I did.
先我一步找到了他
As you know...
如你所知
there's just no stopping a hungry Hollowgast!
没什么能阻止饥饿的灵人捕食
Speaking of my traveling companion...
说到我那个同伴
he's coming.
他已经在来的路上了
Believe me when I say to you...
劝你还是相信我说的
you don't want to be here...
当他到这儿之后
when he arrives.
你绝对不会想留下来了
So, let's be on our way.
我们继续往前走吧
Shall we?
请吧
Excuse me.
借过
Wait for me.
等等我
I mustn't forget our calendar.
日历必须要拿上
Could you fetch it from the parlor
能帮我去客厅拿一下吗
please, Miss Avocet?
艾娃塞小姐？
Go and help the others.
去帮助其他人吧
Miss Peregrine, what a pleasure
佩小姐
to meet you at last!
终于有机会见到你了！
May we come in?
我们能进来吗？
Children!
孩子们
Would you make your way down the stairs, please?
你们都下来吧
I give the orders in this house, Mr. Barron.
巴伦先生！这座房子里轮不到你来下命令
Not today.
今天不行
You should know that Jake has served his purpose.
杰克已经完成他的任务
If you value his life, I suggest
如果你们还想保他的命，我建议
everyone does as they're told.
听我的！
Children! Shush!
- 孩子们！ - 嘘！
No one tells my children what to do!
没人可以命令他们
Children...
孩子们
come down here, please.
都下楼到这里来吧
Miss Peregrine...
佩小姐
I thought I told you to be quiet.
我说过让你安静！
Children...
孩子们
for Jake's safety...
为了杰克的安全
we're going to do what Mr. Barron asks.
我们现在要按巴伦先生说的做
He wishes to take me with him
他希望我
to his rendezvous in Blackpool.
跟他一起去黑池
So, for his protection...
为了保护自己
he'd like me to assume bird form,
他希望我变成鸟的样子
preferably caged.
最好是在笼子里
He'd like you to make your way into a lockable room,
他还想把你们也全部锁起来
such as the parlor...
比如客厅
as he won't release Jake if he fears
如果令他感到
an attack could be mounted upon him...
有一丝的不安全
once he loses his leverage.
他都不会放杰克走
Correct, Mr. Barron?
是这样么，巴伦先生？
You're sacrificing yourself and all of us...
你准备牺牲自己和我们
for Jake?
仅仅为了救杰克？
Mr. Barron travels with a Hollow, Enoch.
巴伦先生带着一只空灵，伊诺克
Once it arrives here, we're all dead.
它一旦来这里，我们都得死
Enoch. Only Jake can see them.
伊诺克，只有杰克能看到空灵们
She means he's our only hope.
他是我们唯一的希望
It's been my privilege...
能照顾你们
to care for you all.
是我的荣幸
Goodbye, my children.
再见！孩子们
Now let him go.
你现在可以放开他了
Promise me one thing, Jake.
杰克，答应我
That you will try to look after them all.
你会尽力照顾他们所有人
I promise.
我答应你
It's getting dark.
天要黑了
You won't even be able to see their shadows.
到时候连它们的影子都看不到了
We have to stay inside.
我们必须待在房子里
It's the only place we stand a chance.
这样我们或许还有一丝生机
He's quite right. Now, where does
他说的对，佩小姐平时
Miss Peregrine keep her weapon?
都把武器放在哪里？
In there. Let's go.
这边，跟我来
Now, all right, children.
孩子们
Make sure all the doors are locked,
去把每一扇门窗
and the windows are latched.
都关好，锁好
Everything must be sealed up tight. Now quickly.
全都牢牢关好，快去
Quickly! Go!
快去！
Here.
这儿
Jake, I think tonight, you better answer that.
杰克，最好你去接
Okay.
好
Hello?
喂？
Hello, this is Abe.
你好，我是亚伯
Who's that?
你是哪位？
You don't know me yet. I'm Jake.
你…你不认识我，我是杰克
Ah, you're new. Welcome to the family, Jake.
哦，你是新来的，欢迎来到这个大家庭，杰克
Now, I can't talk long...
我不能讲太久
so just tell Miss Peregrine...
帮我告诉佩小姐
I'm at the air base, and I'm fine.
我在空军基地，我一切都好
I just wanted to say that I miss you...
我想告诉你，我很想你
and if I disappointed you...
如果我让你失望了
I'm sorry.
对不起
You're the best grandpa in the world.
还有，你是世界上最好的爷爷
Fiona. Got it.
菲奥娜！
Miss Avocet.
艾维赛小姐！
Now, children.
孩子们
Now that you're all here, there's a few rules.
有几条命令大家要记住
Your primary job is to stay safe.
你们一定要保证自己的安全
Leave the Hollow to me.
空灵留着我来对付
I don't want to see any heroics.
千万不要逞英雄
Now those of you with garden tools...
拿着农具的孩子，要记住
I must insist that you...
你们…
No, Enoch. Get back!
不，伊诺克！回来！
Go. Get to the attic!
快跑！去阁楼
Take her.
接着她！
Go. Get out!
走！走！
Olive, come on!
奥利芙，快走！
Crap! It's almost reset!
糟了！要到重置时间了
Fiona, is there anything you can do with that tree?
菲奥娜，你能让那棵树长过来么？
Be careful.
小心点！
We're going through the windows.
我们从这边窗户出去
Let's go! Quickly!
快走，快一点！
Come on!
过来！
Claire, come on down.
克莱尔！快下来
Be careful.
小心点
Go, Fiona!
菲奥娜，快走！
Let's go!
快跑！
- Was that... - The loop closing.
- 怎么回事？ - 时间圈关闭了
It's gone.
全都没了
I'm sorry, Jake.
对不起，杰克
What do we do now?
我们现在怎么办？
Is there any sign of Barron and Miss Peregrine?
有没有巴伦和佩小姐的踪迹？
Gone. Barron must have had a boat.
他们走了，巴伦一定是乘船走了
We have to go after them.
我们必须去找他们
We know he's taking her to Blackpool.
至少我们知道他们要去黑池
But Blackpool is miles away.
黑池离这儿那么远
The next ferry doesn't go for hours.
况且下一班船要再等好几个小时
We'll never make it in time.
我们来不及了
Not unless we go by boat, too.
除非我们现在就有条船！
So, there's a loop here in Blackpool.
在黑池这里有一个时间圈
It's only six months old. January 11th, 2016.
只有六个月，是2016年1月11号
With Miss Avocet gone, it can't be reset.
但现在艾维赛小姐不在了，这个时间圈就无法维持
Won't the loop close?
时间圈会关闭么？
Then it's back to real time.
它就会回到现实时间
Jake, you know what this means, don't you?
杰克，你知道这意味什么么？
You're gonna die.
你会死
That's not what I mean.
我不是这个意思
We have to get to our own time,
我们需要回到自己的时间里
but you don't.
但你不用
You can continue to live in 2016.
你可以继续生活在2016年
But why would I do that?
为什么？
If we kill Barron...
如果我们杀死巴伦
he'll be gone, but time will carry on.
他死了，时间会继续向前
He won't go to Florida...
他就不会去佛罗里达
Abe won't die, and you can go home.
亚伯不会死，你也可以回家了
I could see my grandpa.
我能看到爷爷了
Listen, I can explain everything to them.
我可以向他们解释发生的所有事情！
I can persuade them to take me to the island and...
我可以让他们再带我回到岛上
Wait, will you still be there?
你们还会在那里么？
Our old loop's gone for good.
我们的旧时间圈永远结束了
We wouldn't see each other again.
我们不会再见的
I thought you wanted me to stay.
我以为你想让我留下来
I know you'll choose Abe.
我知道你更想见到亚伯
If I minded, I wouldn't have told you
如果我真想你留下，就不会告诉你这些了
So, have you found Miss Avocet's
找到艾维赛小姐的
loop on the map yet?
时间圈了么？
It's here. But it's new.
在这里，是新建的
She made it early this year. That's my year.
是今年初刚建立的
If we don't get out before it closes,
如果我们不能在时间圈关闭前出来
we're stuck in January 2016.
我们都要被困在2016年1月了
Great.
很好！
Time catches up with all of us,
我们全都被时间困住
we all die, except you. Plan?
都会死，除了你！有什么计划么？
The loop closes at 4:30.
时间圈在4:30关闭
That means we need to get in,
我们需要抓紧进入时间圈
rescue the Ymbrynes and then get out.
救出回时鸟，然后尽快出来
Yeah, if we're not already dead.
前提是我们还活着
Miss Avocet said the machine is in the cellar
艾维赛小姐说过机器
of the Blackpool Tower building.
在黑池塔的地窖里
That means we will be indoors... with Hollows.
也就是说我们要跟空灵面对面
No, we won't. I've got a plan.
不…不需要！我有一个计划
But I'm gonna need your help.
但我需要你们的帮助
This can't be it, can it?
不会是这里吧？
Loop entrances can be anywhere.
任何地方都可能是时间圈入口？
The one in London's in a subway tunnel.
在伦敦的入口是一个地铁隧道
Are you sure this is it?
你确定是这个？
I think so.
我觉得是
Millard, there's something I need you to do first.
米拉德，我现在需要你…
All right. I know.
我知道
Look. There's the tower. It's not far.
看！那就是黑池塔，不远
Easy for you to say. I'm freezing.
说得简单！我可冻死了
Ready?
准备好了么？
All of the doors to the cellar are locked.
所有通往地窖的通道都被封了
The only way to reach the Ymbrynes is through there.
唯一能找到回时鸟的路就是那里
It's backstage.
就是通过那个后台
How many Hollows can you see?
你能看到多少个空灵
Four. That's good news.
4个，算是个好消息
I think you and I have
咱俩对好消息的
very different definition of good news.
定义可不同
It means Barron's other friends haven't arrived yet.
这也就意味着巴伦的其他朋友还没到…
So they haven't started the experiment.
他们还没开始做实验
We're not too late.
所以我们还不晚
Okay, Emma.
艾玛
You ready? You know what to say.
你好了么？你知道要说什么
Here, Jake.
杰克
Our brethren should be joining us momentarily.
其他兄弟马上就会来加入我们
This is a day to...
今天是个…
You down there!
下面的听着
We killed your Hollow friend, Mr. Barron.
巴伦先生，我们杀了你的空灵兄弟
And now we've come for Miss Peregrine.
现在我们来救佩小姐了
Bring her and all the other Ymbrynes
五分钟内带着佩瑞格林小姐
to the end of the pier in five minutes...
和其他的回时鸟去码头
or face the consequences.
不然有你好看的
These children must be
这些孩子们一定是
as insane as their headmistress.
像他们的校长一样疯了
Still, the Hollows will be glad of a feed.
空灵们可是很喜欢饱餐一顿呢
Where are you?
你们在哪儿呢？
I know you're in here somewhere!
我知道你们在这儿
Good. Listen to me.
听着
I want you to follow Mr. Archer and Mr. Clark.
我要你们跟着阿彻先生和克拉克先生
They're going to take you down to the pier...
他们会带你们去码头
for a little afternoon tea.
吃个下午茶
Mr. Archer, Mr. Clark...
阿彻先生，克拉克先生
gather the Hollows and take them to the pier.
请带着空灵们去码头吧
Those children killed Malthus?
这几个孩子杀了马尔萨斯？
Barron's had it in for Malthus
自从马尔萨斯杀了亚伯·波特曼
ever since he killed Abe Portman.
巴伦先生就想干掉他
I tracked Abe Portman for months.
我跟踪了他好几个月
All I needed was a few minutes...
我当时只需要几分钟
to get the location of Miss Peregrine's loop from him.
来问出佩小姐的时间圈地址
But no!
但是不行
Malthus couldn't wait.
马尔萨斯等不及
Instead...
所以呢
I had to masquerade as a psychiatrist...
我就必须得在那
for three weeks...
待上三个星期
in Florida!
伪装成心理医生
Have you ever been to Florida?
你去过佛罗里达么？
Did I not tell you to gather the Hollows?
我不是让你们带着空灵们去码头？
What if it's a trap?
万一是个陷阱怎么办
Of course, it is, Miss Edwards. But what of it?
爱德华小姐，肯定是个陷阱咯，但那又怎样？
A couple of children against four Hollows.
几个小屁孩对空灵就是自寻死路
Let's get this over with.
赶紧行动啊
Jake, I'm stuck!
杰克，我被电线卡住了
Hurry up!
快！
Watch out!
小心
They're coming!
他们来了！
Let's go.
快走
Enoch. Now!
就现在伊诺克！
Go! Now!
动手！
Starting to see them now.
可以看见了
Phase two.
第二步
Emma, go.
艾玛！快！
Don't just stand there. Get them!
别傻站在这儿！去抓住他们！
All right. Good job, guys. It's time for step two.
干得好，孩子们，可以开始第二步计划了
Save Miss Peregrine!
救出佩瑞格林小姐
That's sort of step three.
呃…那算是第三步
First, we've got to deal with Barron.
在这之前我们得先把巴伦解决了
They should've been back by now.
他们现在该回来了
I said it was a trap.
我就说是个陷阱
If that's true...
如果真是这样
perhaps we should move the Ymbrynes now.
我们要转移回时鸟了
You're not serious?
你认真的么？
Do I not look serious?
我看起来像开玩笑的么？
Do I not look like a man who has searched the globe...
是谁跋山涉水
looking for just one more eye to eat...
就为了多吃一个眼睛
in hopes of regaining sufficient humanity...
多点儿人性
to return to his research?
好继续他的研究？
A man who's spent years hunting Ymbrynes...
是谁不遗余力花费数年
in preparation for this night...
抓起这些回时鸟就为了今晚？
and two, no, three days, in Wales...
整整两…不…三天都待在威尔士
pretending to look at birds!
装作在观鸟
I assure you...
我告诉你
I will not stand idly by...
我不会傻傻站在这里
to see my destiny derailed.
眼看着一切脱离我的计划
Hugh, do it now!
休，就现在！
Come back here!
回来！
Get them!
给我抓住他们！
Go. Get down!
下去！
You think you can stand in my way?
你以为你能阻止我？
You, Jake, content to age and die...
杰克，如果你没有这点儿异能
as if you had not the gift of peculiarity at all?
你是不是就满足于生老病死的生活？
I am a higher being.
我更高级
I hold the secret to eternal life!
我知道永生的方法
Sorry to interrupt.
抱歉，打扰一下
What the...
什么…
Bronwyn.
布朗温
You missed me again, Jake.
杰克，你又没打中
I take it accuracy is not your peculiarity.
我猜射的准肯定不是你的异能吧
Abe was a much worthier adversary.
亚伯比你强多了
Don't let him get to the birds.
别让他接近回时鸟！
You must put me in contact with your tailor.
你可得跟我介绍一下你的裁缝
Ymbrynes, Ymbrynes! Here I come!
回时鸟…回时鸟…我来啦！
Cold?
冰冻
Wait till the blood freezes in your veins.
直到血液都凝固
That was your attempt to rescue your friend, was it?
你就打算这么救你朋友？
Jake.
杰克！
I'll hold him off as long as I can.
我尽量拖住他
When are you going to realize
你什么时候才能明白
you are a terrible shot with that thing.
自己准头有多差？
Get the others. I'll meet you at the loop entrance.
带上其他人，我们在时间圈入口那里见
Let's get you out.
我这就救你出来
Eventually...
反正最后
you're going to run out of breath.
你也会没气可吹
And it'll all be over!
窒息而死
Death for your beloved Jake and Miss Peregrine...
为你亲爱的杰克和佩小姐…
everlasting life for me!
还有为了我的永生而死
And a mint for you.
你该吃点薄荷了
Olive.
奥丽芙！
I'm so sorry, Olive.
对不起，奥丽芙
All these years, I never appreciated you.
这么多年我都没珍惜你
I didn't see how lucky I was.
我一直不知道自己有多幸运
I got so used to having you there, I never realized...
我习惯了你一直陪在我身边，从没意识到
You never realized what?
没意识到什么？
Find your children. Create new loops.
找到你们的孩子们，创造新的时间圈
So, Jake...
杰克
I see you've inherited your grandfather's peculiarity.
原来是继承了你祖父的异能
You're just as annoying as he was.
就是像他一样讨厌
Speaking of Abe...
说到亚伯
if you should see him in the afterlife...
记得你死后要是看见他
give him my regards.
替我问候他
Please. We can't risk him taking you again.
不能再让他带走你了
Enoch! Where are the others?
伊诺克！其他人呢？
They're safe. Olive is leading them back to the Ghost Train.
他们都很安全，奥丽芙正带他们回船上
Jake needs us. Barron's too strong.
杰克需要我们，巴伦太强了
You've lost Miss Peregrine.
你现在没了佩小姐
You've lost everything. It's over.
你什么都没了！结束了！
Jake?
杰克？
Emma?
艾玛？
No, wait. Look. That's not me. It's Barron.
等一下，那不是我，那是巴伦
Don't listen to him.
别听他的
He's Barron. No, I'm Jake.
他才是巴伦，我是杰克
That's Barron.
他是巴伦
I've got a better shot than Jake.
我比杰克准的多
So, neither of you move until we sort this.
你俩最好都给我别动
Listen to me. I'm Jake.
听着，我是杰克
I grew up in Florida and I wanted to be an explorer.
我家在佛罗里达，梦想成为探险家
I thought nothing would ever change because I was ordinary.
我认为一切都不会改变，因为我很普通
That's Jake. Get Barron.
他是杰克，那是巴伦
No. Look. I told him all of this.
等一下！他是我心理医生
She was my psychiatrist.
这些都是我告诉他的
Look, you deal with him. I'll go find Miss Peregrine.
你们来对付他，我去找佩小姐
Wait.
等一下
Look, I can prove that I'm me...
我可以证明自己
because I'm not ordinary.
因为我并不普通
I can do something no one else can
我能做的事情别人不行
I can see the monsters.
我能看到那怪物
No, wait. It's me!
看看，是我！
Enoch!
伊诺克！
We need to go. The loop is closing.
我们得走了，时间圈要关了
Those of us who are leaving.
我们要走了
Emma.
艾玛…
You love your grandfather.
你爱你祖父
There's nothing more to explain.
其他的就不用多说了
No, I promised Miss Peregrine I'd look after you all.
不，我答应了佩小姐照顾你们
And with her injured, and you without a loop...
现在她受伤了，你们也不在时间圈里
She'll recover.
她会康复的
Until then, we'll be in 1943.
到那之前，我们继续生活在1943年
We'll only age one day at a time.
只是像普通人一样
Like normal people.
经历时间而已
Which can be no bad thing.
这也不是什么坏事
What about the Hollows?
那空灵怎么办？
As long as they're out there, you're not safe.
只要他们还在，你们就不安全
We don't need you to make us feel safe, Jake.
杰克，没有你我们也能安全
Because you made us feel brave.
因为你已经教给我们更好的
And that's even better.
你让我们勇敢
Come on, guys. Let's go.
伙伴们，走吧！
Tygrysku.
小老虎
And then we said goodbye...
之后我们就道别了
and the loop closed.
时间圈关闭了
I was so scared that you wouldn't be here.
我害怕你不在这儿了
That I'd never see you again.
我就再也见不到你了
I'm safe.
我很好
Let me give you your birthday present.
我要送你生日礼物
Grandpa, my birthday isn't for months.
爷爷，我的生日还有好几个月呢
For your travels.
这是你的路费
Go to her, Jake.
杰克，去找她吧
You have the map.
你有地图
You can get back to 1943.
你能回到1943年
No. Even so, they took a boat.
但他们在船上
I don't know where they are.
我不知道他们现在在哪儿
But you know where they were.
但你知道他们曾经在哪儿
You have no idea how long it took me to get here.
你是不知道我怎么过来的
The closest loop was in the California desert.
最近的时间圈在加利福尼亚沙漠
I used it to get to the Tokyo loop.
我从那里去了东京的时间圈
And that led me to the nearest loop back in 1942...
然后又去了离这儿最近的1942年时间圈
where I wound up joining the Navy.
我参加了海军还受伤了
Don't ask.
这就别多问了
Then I spent two months in London trying to...
之后我在伦敦待了两个月想要…
Ready for full speed ahead!
准备好，加速前进！